nice to meet you.
初めまして
It's so cute.
めちゃめちゃ可愛いすね
thank you.
ありがとうございます
I was a little surprised.
ちょっとびっくりしましたよ
I'm embarrassed.
照れます
The camera is already rolling, but
もうカメラ回っちゃってるんですけど、
Is your son nervous?
息子が緊張されてますか?
Yes, I'm really nervous.
はい、めっちゃ緊張してます
Sorry for my small voice.
声ちっちゃくてごめんなさい
No, it's totally fine.
いやいや、全然大丈夫です
Um, what is that?
あの、何だろう
I want to take control of my nest.
巣の自分をとりたいんで
It's okay if you stay in the nest today.
今日は巣でいてくれたら いいんで
I'm sure you're quite nervous, so let's talk a little bit first.
かなり緊張されてると思うので、 最初にちょっとお話というか、
Can I ask you some questions?
何かいろいろ聞いちゃっていいですか?
If you can't answer something, you don't have to answer.
何か答えられなかったら別に答えなくていいんで
Well, first of all, what is your current occupation?
じゃあまず、 今何かご職業は何されてるんですか?
normally.
普段
At a clothing store.
服屋さんで
I work in apparel.
アパレルで働いてます
It's apparel.
アパレルなんですね
It's really just an image,
何かあの、本当にイメージですけど、
She's so cute, I wonder if she's related to entertainment or something.
こんなに可愛いんで、 何 か芸能関係とか、
I was wondering if you were doing that.
やってらっしゃるのかなと思ったんですけど
I've never done it before.
したことないです
Have you ever been called out to?
声かけられたとこもないですか?
No.
ないです
I can't see it.
見る目ないね
I'd probably go for that.
俺ならそっこうかけるけどね
picture?
え?
happy.
嬉しい
What type of clothing store is a clothing store?
服屋さんは何系の服屋というか、 何 かお店とか、
Can you tell me where you work?
どこで働いてって言える?
Jera Piqué.
ジェラピケ
I mean, it's a clothing store, room wear, things, etc.
服屋さんっていうか、 ルームウェアやシングとか、
Handkerchiefs and detergent.
ハンカチとか洗剤とか
By the way, which store is this?
ちなみにどこの店舗なんですか?
I can't say.
言えません
Can't you say that?
それは言えない?
I can't say.
言えません
Why?
なんでやもう
Well then, it's okay if you overlook it, just sneak up on it.
じゃあ、目見落ちでいいから、 こそっとでいい
from.
から
Well, there are a lot of them.
まあ、 でもいっぱいあるもんね
There's one in Osaka too.
大阪にもあるもんね
So, are you usually from Osaka?
じゃあ、普段大阪の 出身ですか?
That's also a secret.
それも秘密で
The more secrets you have, the better.
秘密が多いほうがいいですね
You're sitting on a mysterious phone.
神秘の電話に座ってますね
Well, I think today is shrouded in that secret.
じゃあ、今日はね、 その秘密に包まれてると思うんですけど、
Today is a little more secular, or rather,
今日はちょっと セキュラーにというか、
I think I'll bring a little veil to you.
いろいろちょっとベールをね、 持っていこうかな
and.
と
Do you have any hobbies?
なんか 趣味とかあるんですか?
cooking.
料理
cooking?
料理?
It's homely.
家庭的ですね
What have you made recently?
最近何作ったとかある?
Like hamburgers.
ハンバーグとか
nice.
いいね
Do you usually cook for yourself?
普段も自炊なの?
Sometimes I cook for myself, and sometimes I make sweets.
自炊するときもあるし、 お菓子作りとかもします
I can make sweets.
お 菓子作れるんだ
Cookies or something.
クッキーとか
You'll be very popular.
めっちゃモテるでしょ
If only she were this cute with such a hobby of cooking.
そんな料理趣味でこんなに可愛かったら
There's not much to show off.
あんまり披露するところがないです
What, you don't have a boyfriend anymore?
え、もう彼氏さんいないですか?
I'm not there.
いないです
By the way, how long have you been gone?
ちなみに前の、 もうどれぐらいいないの?
About a year.
1年ぐらい
Do you want a boyfriend?
彼氏欲しいと思う?
think.
思う
So now that you have a boyfriend, where would you like to go for the first time?
じゃあ今、彼氏できたらさ、初出道どこ行きたいですか?
I want to go from the water tribe.
水族から行きたい
Water tribe?
水 族か
While watching a dolphin show?
イルカショーとか見ながら?
I also want to go to the movies.
映画とかも行きたい
Then there's the person who will take you.
じゃあ連れてってくれる人もね
Actually, I would like to run as a candidate.
本当は僕がちょっと立候補したいんですけど、
Because you're not interested in me.
ちょっと僕のことは興味ないから
What do you think about it?
無 茶苦茶どうですか?
I just met you and talked a little bit.
僕 さっきお会いして、 ちょっとお話しして、
I'm currently in a hotel, and my first impression is...
今ホテル入ってるんですけど、 第一印象というか、
What was it like?
どんな感じでした?
It's like a strange guy has arrived.
変なやつ来たーみたいな
kind.
優しい
kind?
優しい?
Is it a lie?
嘘か
Lies, lies, lies.
嘘嘘嘘
Is it possible in terms of appearance?
見た目的にはありかなしか?
I'll say it.
言 うと
Yes.
ありです
Sorry, I shook my head, but now.
すみません、首横振ったけど今
I think it's okay to judge people by their appearance.
人を見た目で判断していいかなっていう、
Next on this.
次のこれで
Doesn't that mean nothing?
無しって意味じゃない?
Isn't he a really good boy?
めちゃめちゃ良い子じゃないですか?
He's a really good kid.
めっちゃ良い子ですね
What do you do on your day off?
お休みの日は何してるんですか?
I often go out on my days off.
お休みの日はお出かけが多いです
I went out yesterday too.
昨日もお出かけしてました
what have you been up to?
何してたの?
I went to a fan shop and turned off the fan, etc.
ファン屋さん行って ファン止めたりとか、
I usually buy shopping accessories, etc.
普通に 買い物アクセサリーとか買ったり、
I looked at it and tried it on.
見たり、 試着したりしました
That's good.
いいっすね
I sleep on my days off, so I stay in bed all the time.
お休みの日って寝てるから、 ず っとベッドの上よ
There are days like that.
そういう日もあります
Sometimes it's just when I watch YouTube.
YouTube見る時だけの時もある
That's also a hobby.
それも趣味です
What do you think?
どうですか?
Just a little bit, we haven't been able to talk much yet,
ちょっとだけ、まだそんなにおしゃべりできてないですけど、
How do you feel more nervous than before?
ちょっと さっきよりは緊張感どうですか?
I'm doing more than before.
もっと、さっきよりもっとしてます
I'm nervous.
緊 張が
Did it swell?
膨らんじゃった?
Yeah.
うん
Why are you so nervous?
なん でさあ、 そんなに緊張してるんですか?
Isn't the camera filming you?
カメラの撮られてるじゃないですか?
I'm nervous in front of the camera because I don't know what I'm going to do today.
カメラの前で、 今日はどういうことをするから緊張されてます
mosquito?
か?
Something naughty?
イ ッチなこと?
Ah, that's right.
ああ、そうですね
Just being photographed by a camera,
普通にカメラ撮られてるだけじゃ、
You're not nervous, are you?
緊張しないでしょ?
Just talking normally.
普通に喋ってるだけで
That also makes me nervous.
それも緊張するんだ
He was touching my hair and moving his hands,
髪の毛触ってたり、 手を動かしてたりするんで、
I get nervous because I try not to be nervous,
緊張しないようにと思って緊張するし、
I don't have much experience with naughty things, so
イッチなことも、 経験がそんなにないので、
I'm nervous.
緊張します
The only boyfriend I've ever dated,
今まで付き合ってきた彼氏さんだけ、
What is your experience?
経験は?
One night or something like that?
ワンナイトとかそういうの?
One night, or rather, with someone I like.
ワンナイトというか、 好きな人で、
Although it didn't come true, I do have some fond memories.
叶わなかったけど、 片思い出っていうのはあります
That's right.
それはね
It's pretty well connected to the lower tiers.
結構低層関連しっかりされてますね
Low-rise related?
低層関連?
Are you okay today?
今日大丈夫ですか?
I'm just nervous and things like dates don't go well.
緊張して、 デートとかがうまくいかないだけです
I can't drink, so I also have alcohol.
飲めないので、お酒も
I'm not good at drinking parties, so I didn't have many opportunities to do that.
飲み会とかも苦手なので、 そういうチャンスが少なかった
It's just that.
っていう だけです
I might be a little rude, but
ちょっと失礼かもしれないですけど、
Quite naive.
結構ウブ
結 構ウブ
It might be rude.
失礼かもしれない
Well, that's what they say.
まあ、そう言われますね
Is it naive or a little behind the scenes?
ウブというか、ちょっと奥手?
that's right.
そうです
I'm behind the scenes.
奥手です
I'm the type of person who doesn't really like myself.
あんまり自分がいけないタイプですね
It's not my fault.
自分がいけないですね
But no, if there is that slight disturbance,
でもいいや、その微妨があったら、
Please do it.
やってくれでしょ
Well, that's not the case.
うーん、 そんなことはないですね
Is that so?
そうかそうか
As you said earlier today,
今日はさっきも言っていただいたんですけど、
If you do something naughty.
エッチなことをしますと
So, I have to ask about that as well.
なので、ちょっと、 そういうことも聞いとかなければいけない
Yes, it is.
んです よ
yes.
はい
Honestly, when it comes to naughty things, I either like them or I don't.
正直、エッチなことは、 好きか嫌いかで言うと
Are you interested or not?
また興味あるかないかでどっちですか?
I'm interested and I like it.
興味あるし、好きです
Do you like it?
好きですか?
Yeah.
うん
What is the erogenous body?
性感体は?
The erogenous organs are the nipples and the inside.
性感体は、乳首とか、 中
I like it better inside.
中のほうが好きですね
If you touch it, it will be inside your hair.
触られたら、 髪 の毛の中とか
In your hair?
髪の毛の中?
Yes, I can feel it on my scalp.
はい、頭皮とか感じます
But I like the nipples the most.
でも、乳首が一番好きです
When making a woman, should I use a medium instead of a chestnut?
女にするときは、 栗じゃなくて中なの?
When it comes to women, it's chestnut.
女にするときは、栗です
I mean, when you make someone a woman, you make them a woman.
女にするときは、 女 にするんだっていうか
When I turned it into a woman, I put my hand inside my computer.
女にするときは、 手を自分で、自分の パソコンの中に入れた
There is no such thing.
こと ないです
Oh, there isn't.
あ、ないんです
Why is that?
なんでそれは?
It's kind of scary.
なんか怖い
I'm scared to be myself.
自分でいるの怖いんだ
Yes, my nails are growing and I have put toys in them.
はい、爪の伸びてるし、 お もちゃを入れたことあるんです
However, I don't understand things like G-SPOT by myself.
けど、 G-SPOTとかが自分で分からなくて、
I just put the toys in and took them out.
おもちゃ入れて出しただけになりました
I couldn't wait until I felt it.
感じるまでいかなかった
Just today, I'm trying to find out something like this.
ちょうど今日、僕ちょっとね、 こう いう のを探ってみる
Well, let me ask you something along the way.
んで、 途中聞いてくね?
Here it is.
ここが
yes.
はい
What do you have as a side dish when making a woman?
女にするときは何をおかずにするの?
comics.
漫画
It's like an erotic manga.
エロ漫画みたいな
I watch naughty manga.
エッチな漫画見るんだ
What kind of situation?
どういうシチュエーションとかが?
Like 3P or 4P.
3Pとか、 4Pみたいな
I'm of a normal height, so the main character is a smaller girl.
私が定身長なので、 小さめの女の子が主人公で、
I was attacked in various ways by two or three men, or something like that.
男性2人3人とかで、 い ろんな攻められるっていうか、
A manga that makes you feel like you're being explored.
探られる感じの漫画
I like manga.
漫画が好きなんですよ
Not a video.
映像じゃなくて
Are you interested in playing like that?
そういうプレイ興味あるんですか?
I'm interested.
興味あります
I'll do my best to make some plans as time goes on.
ちょっとゆくゆく企画できるように頑張ります
This is the last question, what edge has changed so far?
これ最後の質問で、 今まで変わったエッジとか、
Are there any unusual places or situations?
変わった場所、シチュエーションありますか?
Not much.
あまりないですね
I only have the homes of people I like.
好きな人のおうちとかしかないです
Of course, this is the first time I've been photographed on camera like this.
もちろんこうやってカメラに撮られても初?
It's the first time.
初です
No Gonzo or anything?
ハメ撮りとかもない?
I don't do sex movies.
ハメ撮りないですね
I think he was nervous, but he let me take care of him.
緊張したと思うんですけど、 僕で身を任せてもらって
So I feel like it's time to get started.
じゃあもう早速、 そろそろ始めちゃおうかなという感じなんです
But what do you think?
けど、 どうですか?
How are you mentally prepared?
心の準備はどうですか?
It's done.
できました
Did you do it?
できました?
OK.
OKです
So, can I just go aside for a moment?
じゃあちょっと僕横に行っちゃっていいですか?
yes.
はい
This sofa sinks, amazing.
これソファ沈むね、すげえ
It's cute.
可愛いね
You have a really strong face and size.
顔全然強いね、大きさ
not at all.
全然
Look at it, not at all.
見てみて、全然
Are you excited?
ドキドキしてる?
Wow, so much fun.
すごい、バクバクもバクバク
I'll do my best.
頑張るぞ
yes.
はい
Well then,
じゃあ、
I'll do my best to take naughty photos today.
今日は エッチな撮影頑張ります
A big boy came out today.
今日一応大きい子出たね
So, is that enough?
じゃあ、 もういい?
飲
So I decided to have some tea...
んで たので、お茶の...
Are you hydrated?
うるおってる?
I might smell the tea.
お茶の匂いがするかも、私が
So why don't you smell the tea more?
じゃあもっとお茶の匂い確かなきゃいいですか?
What kind of tea were you drinking?
何のお茶飲んでたの?
That's pretty aggressive...
あれ、結構積極的な...
I just looked at it from below.
さっき今、下から見ましたけど
結構...
I asked you to tell me how the tea tastes.
お茶の味を教えてって言ったから
Sorry, it's my fault.
ごめん、俺のせいか
Then, could you tell me more about the taste of tea?
じゃあもうちょっとちゃんとお茶の味を教えてもらっていい?
Don't you hate it?
嫌じゃない?
If you do it with people.
人達とやったら
That's a nice chew.
いいチューだね
No, it feels really good.
いやいや、めっちゃ気持ちいいよ
Do you like chew?
チュー好き?
Don't you hate it?
嫌じゃない?
It's not really spicy, right?
めっちゃ辛くないでしょ?
There isn't.
ないですよ
It's not cute.
可愛くないですよ
It's so cute, can you see it?
めっちゃ可愛すぎてさ、ほら、 見てわかる?
What?
何が
Of the stomach.
お腹の
I understand.
わかる
No matter what.
何がたって
Because it's cute.
可愛いからさ
It's so cute that it's going to get really big.
可愛いからもうめっちゃ大きくなっちゃう
Isn't it tiring?
しんどくない?
That's it.
それね
Just like that, my lips are here too.
ちょうどさ、俺のちくびもここにあるんだよ
Oh no, it's gotten bigger again.
あ、やばい、また大きくなっちゃった
It's gotten bigger.
大きくなっちゃった
It's a little too cute, so give it a squeeze from behind.
ちょっと可愛すぎるから、 後ろからギュッって押して
behind?
後ろ?
My stomach might be protruding.
お腹が出てるかも
Touch the part that was sticking out more.
もっと出てた部分を触って
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
By the way, what did you buy?
ちなみに、何買ったの?
It's D.
Dです
D?
get nervous?
緊張する?
get nervous.
緊張する
It's coming out a lot.
めっちゃ出ちゃってるよ
Too much right skirt.
右スカートすぎて
Well then, I want to touch it carefully.
じゃあ、 よく触りたいからさ
Just sit here normally like before.
さ っきみたいにここ普通に座って
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Very bright.
明るい、めっちゃ
Why don't you have sex in a bright place like this?
こんな明るいところでエッチしない?
Is it always electric?
いつも電気です?
I've never done it before.
したことないです
Is it always electric?
いつも電気です?
It's okay.
大丈夫ですよ
Well, if it's embarrassing for me to do it,
じゃあ、俺がやるのが恥ずかしいんだったらさ、
Can you flip it yourself?
自分でめくってくれる?
Is that no good either?
それもダメ?
No.
ダメ
By yourself?
自分で?
Well, since I won't look at it, can I touch it?
じゃあ、見ないから触っていい?
Do it yourself
自分でこう
Do it.
やって
yes?
そう?
Too deep.
深 すぎる
Well then, just this one.
じゃあ さ、こっちだけさ
You can touch me often.
よく触らせていいからさ
Why are you smiling?
なんで笑ってるんですか?
Hey, look carefully.
ほ ら、ちゃんと見して
What kind of place is being touched now?
今触られてるところ、 なんていうところ?
What do you call the whole thing?
全体なんていうのか?
It's very sensitive.
めっちゃ敏感じゃん
It's nothing.
なんでもないです
I'm nervous.
緊張してる
What should I do?
どうするの?
like this
こう
What does it feel like?
いう 感じ?
I like that.
それ好きです
Do you like horizontal?
横好き?
I like horizontal.
横好きです
what up?
どうした?
sorry.
ごめんなさい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいいってこと?
Well then, I'll give you some water to drink.
じゃあ水、ちょっと俺が くつうすしで飲ませようか
It's so erotic.
めっちゃエロいね
Was it your first time?
初回いた?
get nervous.
緊張する
Does it feel close?
近くに感じるんだっけ?
Because you touch it directly.
直接触るから
Are you going to project it?
映すの?
I'll show it.
映すよ
It's so beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗じゃん
めちゃめちゃ綺麗だね
It's a bee cup.
ビーカップです
How big did it get?
いつぐらいに大きくなってきたの?
About junior high school
中学校ぐらい
To.
に
Around middle school.
中 学校ぐらいに
What are you going to do?
どうするんですけ?
I'll leave it to you.
お任せします
About junior high school?
中学校ぐらい?
Well, come on, sit a little shallower.
じゃあさ、 ちょっとさ、 ちょっと浅めに座って
It's higher.
もっと高くあって
Raise your legs.
足あげて
both.
両方
Raise both legs.
足両方あげて
It's so beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗じゃん
You can't see it, right?
見られないでしょ?
Ah, okay.
あ、いいよ
Just leave it as is.
普通そのままで
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしいよ
It's beautiful.
綺麗だよ
Your pussy is so beautiful.
マンコめっちゃ綺麗じゃん
I've never been told that.
言われたことないんです
Her pussy is so beautiful.
めっちゃマンコ綺麗だ
Please don't say that.
そんなこと言わないでください
Are you embarrassed?
恥ずかしい?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It's long.
長いですよ
Are you embarrassed to open it?
開くの恥ずかしい?
Please don't do that.
そんなことしないでください
It feels good but embarrassing.
気持ちいいけど恥ずかしい
Which one is stronger?
どっちの方が強い?
Okay.
いいよ
Take it out.
出して
There are a lot of strange kids
変 な子いっぱいじゃ
yeah.
ん
That's it.
あれ だよね
I really like it.
なかなか好きなんだもんね
I like what's inside.
中は好きですよね
I like boobs the most.
おっぱいが一番好きなんです
Do you like boobs?
おっぱいが好き?
yes.
はい
What is that?
それは何?
Do you mean attack your breasts more?
もっとおっぱい攻めてってこと?
I want you to touch me more.
もっと触ってほしい
It feels so good that I almost want to.
きそうなぐらい気持ちいい
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
If you like the inside, try expanding it yourself to make it easier to fit inside.
中が好きだったら入れやすいように自分で広げてみて
Put your hands down yourself.
自分で手を下に回して
The feeling for the first time.
初めての感覚
It's the first time.
初のことです
first time?
初?
Have you never expanded it?
広げたことないの?
Not even me.
自分でもないし
You mean you've never seen it yourself?
自分も見たことないってこと?
I've never seen it before though.
見たことないことはないですけどね
I see it in the bathroom.
お風呂とかで見るけど
Would you like to take a look?
見てみる?
Is there something going on today?
今日は何かあるんでしょ
It's completely gone.
めっちゃ消えてる
Ah, this.
あ、これ
amazing.
すごい
I can see your face too.
顔も映ってる
Amazing composition.
すごい構図
This shows my face.
これ顔映ってる
Pull it.
引いて
That's amazing.
すごいじゃん
I'm so wet.
めっちゃ濡れてる
Please don't show it.
見せないでください
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
I don't feel like it yet.
まだ気持ちくないです
Maybe if it was moved sooner...
多分早めに動かされたら...
high speed.
高速
I don't know if it's slow.
ゆっくりだと分からないです
I like it intense.
激しいのが好きなんだ
Be early.
早めで
Which do you prefer, having your dreams taken out or being fucked?
夢を出し入れされるのと グッグッされるのどっちが好き?
I get jerked off.
グ ッグッされるの
like this?
こう?
Well then, let's go.
じゃあ行くよ
like this?
こう?
Are you fiddling with your fingers?
指こういじる?
Ah, there.
あ、そっち
So let's make the fingers longer.
じゃあもっと長い指にやろうか
Is it different?
違うんですか?
Are you changing your fingers?
指変えるんですか?
That's right.
そうだよ
I don't know if I should try or not.
しようかどうか分かんないけど
It was popping out.
ピュッて出てたよ
Pyutte.
ピ ュッて
That's impossible.
それは無理だよ
Well then, I'll go for a little while.
じゃあさ、 もうちょっと行くからさ
Try sitting down and sweating a little.
一回ちょっと汗見え座ってみて
One finger longer?
指1本長い?
2 long?
2本長い?
One?
1本?
Make one, make it big,
1本して、大きいして、
Which was better, one finger or two?
指 1本、2本、どっちがよかった?
Well, let's go to the finishing machine, because I want it to be close to the camera.
じゃあさ、 仕上げ機にさ、 カメラの近くに収めたいからさ、
It's a little messy here.
ちょっとさ、 よふけてるよ、ここ
What do you want instead of fingers?
指じゃなくて何が欲しい?
Come here.
こっちおいで
Well, first I want you to prepare mine.
じゃあ さ、 まず俺ののさ、 準備して欲しいからさ、
Can you lick my nipples?
乳首から舐めてくれる?
Can I take it off?
脱がしていい?
This isn't perfect yet, so give it a try.
これまだ完全体じゃないからさ、 ちょっと舐めてさ、
Make it bigger.
もっと大きくしてよ
Lick it from the head.
頭から舐めて
Are you licking too much?
舐めすぎですか?
Is it easy to do?
やりやすい?
Yeah.
うん
Is it rolled up?
巻き上がってる?
Does it hurt?
痛いですか?
So, raise it up to about your nose.
で、鼻ぐらいに上げて
Make a cut around the size of your nose.
鼻ぐらいに傷しといて
口開
Kete.
けて
Can I come out?
出 ちゃっていい?
I'll put it in.
入れるよ
Oh, please put your dick in me raw.
あ、生でおちんちん入れてくださいって言って
It feels really good.
ちゃんと気持ちいいじゃん
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
It doesn't hurt.
痛くないよ
never mind.
気にしないで
I've never really moved up.
上に動くの あんまりやったことない
Well then,
じゃあさ、
Put your hand between my legs.
手 を俺の足の間に入れて
Point your hands toward the base of your feet.
手を足の 足しろに向けて
Also, raise your hips a little.
で、お尻もちょっと腰を浮かして
Have you never done it?
やったことない?
Because I move.
俺が動くから
Yeah.
うん
My physical condition is difficult.
体調難しいね
Yeah.
うん
Leave it in and try again.
入れたまま もう一回やって
One more time.
もう一回
Bring your hands in front of you.
手を前に持ってきて
Been a different case.
別の場合になって
Just flatten out your upper body.
上半身だけペタンアウトして
But did it feel good to be normal?
でも正常なのが気持ちよかったの?
Lie down there.
寝転んで、そこに
Get up on your elbows.
肘ついた状態を起こして
I fell asleep so bad.
めっちゃ寝ちゃったよ
What was it like inside and when you came out?
中にさ、 出た時さ、どんな感じだった?
It felt really good.
めっちゃ気持ちよかったです